Christopher M. Grantʼs TimesheetWeek 1 - (6 Hours):1. Drafted the idea/problem (originally wanted to make a Facebook Notification App)2. Storyboarded my design (see attached picture)3. Broke the design / idea into miniproblems(logging users in/out, carrying out an actions for new or read notifications, etc.)4. Assessed what I would need in order to implement:(Facebook Platform API / Toolkit for Python--oAuth for user authentication;Notifications.get feature for scraping "pokes", wallposts, etc; make calls to Facebook'sGraphAPI via the desktop rather than webserver aka the "client-side flow approach";and the Legacy REST API; and Python's webbrowser module;)-The total time spent last week on the above duties and two CA meetups was about 6hours (1 hour per meeting, 4 hours of independent study, research, and drafting).Week 2- (10 hours):Facebook API research, learning Unix commands to install modules via Terminal,resolving and identifying issues. Found documentation to be poor and limited; switchedgears and changed project idea to Facebook Top Friend. Met with mentor for 1 hour.Week 3 (17hrs):Figured out top down design structure. Researched graphic requirements.Met with mentor twice (2hrs). Programmed, debugged, and photoshopped.